(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T23:23:00.408560",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
狂おしいのよ ただ強く抱きしめていたいよ
I'm going crazy, I just want to hold you tight.
もっとギュッと 暗い夜のそこで
Much tighter, at the bottom of the dark night,
少し楽しませて...なんてね
let me enjoy it a little... just kidding.
Chu-La-Peat チャックして 丸ごとパックすると 空の彼方へ
Chu-La-Peat, zip it up, pack it whole, and to the other side of the sky...
Hi-Fi 鳴らせてく 胸躍るスパンコールの音ね
Let's ring the Hi-Fi, heart dancing to the sound of sequins.
Chu-La-Peat Chu-La-Peat 立ち込め 先の未来 誰もが求めるメロディーね
Chu-La-Peat Chu-La-Peat, filling up the future ahead, the melody everyone seeks!
シャキッとキメて 飛んじゃって
Decide sharply and take off!
地球上 どこまでも満たされちゃって
Fill up everywhere on Earth!
Chu-La-Peat Chu-La-Peat 宇宙まで 伝えたい私の 歌声
Chu-La-Peat Chu-La-Peat, I want my singing voice to reach all the way to space!
さあ 時代を越えて
Now, transcending eras,
さあ 次の波へ
now, to the next wave,
さあ 無限大の可能性を乗せて 放て
now, carrying infinite possibilities, unleash it!
Chu-La-Peat チャックして 丸ごとパックすると 空の彼方へ
Chu-La-Peat, zip it up, pack it whole, and to the other side of the sky...
踊れ踊れ
dance, dance!
Chu-La-Peat 巡って 丸ごとパックすると
Chu-La-Peat, going around, pack it whole,
無限に広がる先へ
to where it spreads infinitely.
溢れるだけのスターセーラーから
With just overflowing stars, from Sailor,
センセーション起こすターンターンターン
causing a sensation, turn, turn, turn!
まだ見たことない未来を てってってってって
And for the future we've never seen, let's step, step, step!
照明する 超科学バリア 3, 2, 1
Illuminating super-scientific barrier, 3, 2, 1,
飛び込んで 光る迷いの空
plunge into the shining sky of hesitation!
この闇を駆け抜けると ほら とびきり宇宙放って
Look, as we run through this darkness, releasing a spectacular space!
1人じゃ行けないところまで
To the place where I can't go alone,
連れていってね
take me there.
さあ 時代を越えて
Now, transcending eras,
さあ 次はどこへ
now, where to next?
さあ 巡り続け ずっと時をかけて
Now, continuing to go around, traveling through time forever.
止まらないで 刻む胸のメロディ
Don't stop, the melody ticking in my chest.
今 私たちの未来はここに
Right now, our future is here.
今 どこまでも広がってゆく そう、あの場所へ
Now, spreading out everywhere, yes, to that place!
Chu-La-Peat チャックして 丸ごとパックすると 空の彼方へ 踊れ踊れ
Chu-La-Peat, zip it up, pack it whole, and dance to the other side of the sky!
Chu-La-Peat 巡って 丸ごとパックすると エンドレスビートに身を任せて
Chu-La-Peat, going around, pack it whole, and leave yourself to the endless beat,
無限に広がる先へ
to where it spreads infinitely.
溢れるだけのスターセーラーから
With just overflowing stars, from Sailor,
センセーション起こすターンターンターン
causing a sensation, turn, turn, turn!
まだ見たことない未来を てってってってって
And for the future we've never seen, let's step, step, step!
さあ 時代を越えて
Now, transcending eras,
さあ 次はどこへ
now, where to next?
さあ 巡り続け
Now, continuing to go around,
もっと強く抱きしめていたいよ
I just want to hold you even tighter.
交点 0時 隣の街を
The intersection, midnight, the neighboring town,
独り占めするキープ
keeping it all to myself.
散らばったビル明かり
Scattered building lights,
失ったものばかりかき集めている
gathering only things that have been lost.
目を閉じて うとうと
Closing my eyes, dozing off...
サヨナラって 終われないし
I can't end with a goodbye,
永遠の夜なんてないのはわかってる
I know there's no such thing as an eternal night,
だから...
so...
キミとはぐれる世界
In a world where I lose sight of you,
明日もまた同じ 朝日が昇るなら
if the same morning sun rises again tomorrow...
もう何もいらない
I won't need anything else.
蒼く光る夜空 星空のミラーボール
The blue glowing night sky, a disco ball of stars,
私を照らして
shine down on me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to make the Earth shake with a tap,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away here.
午前5時の夜明けを待って
Waiting for the dawn at 5:00 AM,
なんかひとりぼっちな気分
I feel somewhat all alone.
薄まっていくパレット ぼんやり眺めるベッド
A fading palette, staring blankly from my bed,
期待している キミの足音を
I'm waiting expectantly for the sound of your footsteps.
触れたくても 触れられないし
Even if I want to touch you, I can't,
運命の赤い糸なんて知らないし
and I know nothing of any red thread of fate.
それでもキミと繋がっていたい
Even so, I still want to be connected to you.
明るくなる空に この想い乗せても
Even if I send these feelings into the brightening sky...
もう何も見えない
I can't see anything anymore.
灰色に流れる 雲間から差し込む
Flowing in gray, shining through the clouds...
光の向こうへ
toward the other side of the light,
たっぷり深呼吸して
I take a deep breath
境界線を越える
and cross the boundary line.
暗闇にちりぢり 見える場所
A place visible scattered in the darkness...
裸足で踊る 夜空がまわり
Dancing barefoot, the night sky spins
キラキラ光るの
and shines so brightly.
ねえ 早く気付いて
Hey, notice me quickly,
私を見つけて
and find me.
明日もまた同じ 朝日が昇るなら
If the same morning sun rises again tomorrow...
もう何もいらない
I won't need anything else.
蒼く光る夜空 星空 of ミラーボール
The blue glowing night sky, a disco ball of stars,
私を照らして
shine down on me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to make the Earth shake with a tap,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away here.
なんであなたには理解できないの？ なんてさ
"Why can't you understand me?" I say.
陰口言われたり 呆れられたり 好感度下がるって言われて
Being badmouthed, looked down on, told my popularity would drop...
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind,
刃物や薬もスピード早すぎだね
and knives and pills are just way too fast.
ありのままの素敵な姿じゃ足りない？ Bite me, bite me
Is my natural, beautiful self not enough? Bite me, bite me.
毎日死ぬほど頑張って やっとここまで連れてきたんだ
Working myself to death every day, I finally made it this far.
あなたにはわからない
You will never understand,
わかってほしくない
and I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も首の紐もご存知ないでいてね
Keep my struggles and the rope around my neck unknown to you.
きっとあなたにもできるはず なんてさ
"I'm sure you can do it too," they say.
言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as those words.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って駆ける 価値はあると思った
Still, running and trying my absolute hardest, I thought it was worth it.
投げ出したって軽くなるよ
Throwing it all away would make things easier,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to give up.
私の未来も 失敗も全部 私だけのもの
My future, my failures, they are all mine alone.
あなたにはわからない
You will never understand,
わかってほしくない
and I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も首の紐もご存知ないでいてね
Keep my struggles and the rope around my neck unknown to you.
投げ出したって軽くなるよ
Throwing it all away would make things easier,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to give up.
変わりたい
I want to change,
私の未来も
my future too...
失敗も全部 渡さないよ
I won't give away all of my mistakes.
気づかない 気づかないでいて
Don't notice, please don't notice...
可愛いだけの私でいい
Just being cute is enough for me.
さあ
Now...
La la la...
胸に詰め込んだ
The dreams packed into my chest...
夢はくしゃくしゃで
...are all crumpled,
勇気がいるけど
and it takes courage,
君にだけ見せてよ
but let me show them only to you.
手をとって
Take my hand,
一緒にいこう
and let's go together,
秘密の街を
through the secret town,
渡っていこう
let's cross over.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath,
吸って 吐いて
inhale, exhale,
笑った顔 交代でもらっちゃうくらい
to the point where we exchange our smiling faces.
最高な笑顔を
The greatest smiles...
うまくいかない今日だって 今日だって 歌う
Even on days when things don't go well, today we still sing.
私の教科書
My textbook...
見ずに閉じたら
if I close it without looking,
何だってやれそうだ
it feels like I can do anything.
もっと
More...
瞬いて 記して
Twinkle and mark it down.
La la la...
酸いも甘いも 集めたら
If we gather both the sweet and the sour,
手と手とったら
if we hold hands,
成長できるかな
will we be able to grow?
ともにワルツを
Together we waltz...
ちゃんと
With proper steps,
描いた輪の中に
inside the circle we drew,
自分ぽく立っていられたら
if I can stand in my own way,
楽しかった日々ほら 一瞬で向こう
look, those fun days are gone in an instant,
昨日よりも加速してる
accelerating faster than yesterday,
ちゃんと繋いでて
so hold on tight.
簡単じゃない日々の 駆け声は
The shouts of encouragement during these far-from-easy days,
いつも君が明るく放って
you always call them out brightly
支えてくれる
to support me.
ずっと
Forever,
刻まれた光よ
a light engraved.
三つ数えたら
If I count to three,
砂に描いた絵
the picture drawn in the sand...
消えてしまうけど それと同じで
...will disappear, but in the same way...
君の顔ばかり
...if only your face...
浮かんでたら
...keeps floating in my mind,
アイスみたいに とろけてくわ
I'll melt just like ice cream.
どんな風になる？
...how will it turn out?
夢も愛もギュッとしていっぱいだから
My dreams and love are squeezed tight and full,
もう持ちきれない
so I can't carry them all anymore.
でも欲張りすぎてキープしていく
But I'm being too greedy and keeping them close.
ほら クラクラ中中 恋に落ちちゃって
Look, dizzy, falling head over heels in love,
もう戻れない
and there's no going back!
あれあれ何でふわっと心が
Oh my, why is my heart floating?
まだ熱くなるの？
Is it still heating up?
ほら クラクラ中中 君の重力で
Look, dizzy, pulled by your gravity,
引き寄せて
draw me closer.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope,
ねえ キラキラな未来見たい
hey, I want to see a sparkling future...
わからない
I don't know...
おー、アップアンドダウンで ちょっ振り回す
Oh, tossing and turning up and down,
ようんで今日明日、四六時中
all day and tomorrow, 24/7...
カレンダー30日 でも足りない
30 days on the calendar is not enough.
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything!
きゅんきゅんきゅん上昇、ドキドキ白書
Squeezing and rising, a heart-throbbing white paper!
きゅんきゅんきゅん降下、深呼吸
Squeezing and falling, take a deep breath.
きゅんきゅんきゅん上昇、らぶらぶメーター
Squeezing and rising, the love-love meter!
きゅんきゅんきゅん降下、凸撃と
Squeezing and falling, charge ahead!
無限大の間で 失敗だけど
Even in the midst of infinity, even if I fail,
諦めない
I won't give up.
まだ欲張りだから君と知っていく
Because I'm still greedy, I'll learn with you...
ほら クラクラ中中 心が回って
Look, dizzy, my heart is spinning,
抜け出せない
I can't escape.
あれあれ何で目まぐるしい心が
Oh my, why is my hectic heart
まだ熱くなるの？
still heating up?
ほら クラクラ中中 スピード重視で
Look, dizzy, focusing on speed,
引き寄せて
draw me closer.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope,
ねえ キラキラな未来見たい
hey, I want to see a sparkling future...
わからない
I don't know...
ちっぽけだな 急ぐ私
So tiny, hurrying me,
まだまだ未完成で
still incomplete,
あの空に目をそらしてしまうんだ
I end up averting my eyes from that sky.
考えてもどうしようもないことだと
Even if I think, it's something that can't be helped,
求めな 心から 色々考えてくるけど
seeking from my heart, even though different thoughts come to me.
だからこそ 笑顔でね
That's exactly why, with a smile,
だからこそ 負けないで
that's exactly why, don't give up.
羽ばたくための この両手にして
To flap my wings, holding onto these hands...
飛び立って行くんだよ
I will fly away!
空を飛んで行こう 飛んで行こう 色づいてく夢 ほら見てごらん
Let's fly in the sky, let's fly, look at the dreams taking on color.
青混ぜてみよう 混ぜてみよう 少し大きくなったね
Let's mix in blue, let's mix it, it's grown a little bigger, hasn't it?
空は青い色 青い色 少し経ったらすぐに茜色
The sky is blue, blue, after a little while, it will turn madder red.
ちょっと迷っても 迷っても ゆっくり風を受けて
Even if we get a little lost, a little lost, slowly feel the wind.
右に願いを
A wish on the right,
何度も約束して
promising again and again,
いつしか忘れていた 奇跡の閉じ方を
I had forgotten before I knew it, how to lock away the miracles.
ある時は 笑顔でね
At times with a smile,
ある時は 涙が溢れ
at times with tears overflowing,
見上げた空が 目印にして
letting the sky we look up to guide us,
旅立っていくんだよ 届けて
we will depart on our journey! Deliver it...
空は暗い色 影の色
The sky is dark, the color of shadows.
心がずっと 落ち込んでしまっても
Even if your heart stays downcast,
やがてパステル色 明るい色
soon it'll turn pastel, a bright color,
私がきっと 晴れ晴れにしちゃうから
because I'll definitely clear it up for you!
空のカタチ色 無限だね
The shape and color of the sky is infinite, isn't it?
いつか待ったあの場所で
At that place we once waited,
どんな空色が 見えるかな
what color of the sky will we see, I wonder?
飛べ！飛べ！
Fly! Fly!
エレクトリカル・サーフィン サーフィン
Electrical Surfing, surfing!
こちらに来て来て
Come over here, come on over!
好いも狂いもいただきます
I'll take both the good and the crazy!
サーフィン サーフィン
Surfing, surfing!
手と手とってって
Let's hold hands!
白昼夢中 夢中で踊り明かしましょう
Daydreaming, let's dance the night away!
バーチャル リアル どっち可愛い？
Virtual or real, which one is cuter?
バーチャル リアル どっちも可愛い！
Virtual or real, both are super cute!
ちゅっちゅちゅ ちゅっちゅちゅ チェリーチェリーチュウチュウチュ
Chu, chu, chu! Chu, chu, chu! Cherry, cherry, chu, chu, chu!
サムネタップ始めまして
Nice to meet you, tap that thumbnail!
キュンキュンしたならハート押して
If your heart skips a beat, hit that heart button!
通知はオン いつでもカモン
Turn notifications on, come on anytime!
一緒に踊ろうよ オン・アンド・オン
Let's dance together on and on!
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I wanna eat sweets, but I'm on a diet!
君の好みにアップデート中
Currently updating to your liking!
ポチポチ更新 君と交信
Click, click, update! Communicating with you...
もっと推してほしいの
I want you to support me even more!
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual or real, which one do you like?
繋がってる 123次元
We're connected across 1, 2, and 3 dimensions!
ワンツースリーで飛び越えて
Let's leap over with a one, two, three!
今はもうネットもリアルです
Even the internet is real life now!
チックチック繋いで ラブアンドピース
Connecting tick-tick, love and peace!
ちくたくまわるまわる
Tick-tock, spinning 'round and 'round!
ときめきチャージ ときかけガール
Charging up excitement, a time-traveling girl!
スリーツースリーツースリーワン
Three, two, three, two, three, one!
待てれば大勝利 バーチャリアル
If you can wait, it's a huge win, Virtu-Real!
ちゅっちゅちゅ ちゅっちゅちゅ チェリーチェリーチュウチュウチュ
Chu, chu, chu! Chu, chu, chu! Cherry, cherry, chu, chu, chu!
にわかにスワイプビート足して
Suddenly adding a swipe and a beat!
キュンキュンしたなら手叩いて
If your heart skips a beat, clap your hands!
発信も エンジョイも
Whether streaming or enjoying...
一緒に踊ろうよ オン・アンド・オン
Let's dance together on and on!
お姉ちゃん可愛いけどコラボ中
My big sister is cute, but we're collaborating!
君と楽しいことリサーチ中
Currently researching fun things to do with you!
ピピピテレパシー今日も配信
Pi-pi-pi, telepathy! Streaming today too!
もっとハートほしいの
I want even more hearts!
ねぇねぇ どっち可愛い？
Hey, hey! Which one is cuter?
どっち可愛い？
Which one is cuter?
ねぇねぇ どっち可愛い？
Hey, hey! Which one is cuter?
どっち可愛い？
Which one is cuter?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are super cute!
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I wanna eat sweets, but I'm on a diet!
君の好みにアップデート中
Currently updating to your liking!
ポチポチ更新 君と交信
Click, click, update! Communicating with you...
もっと推してほしいの
I want you to support me even more!
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual or real, which one do you like?
バーチャル リアル どっちも好き！
Virtual or real, I love both!
繋がってる 123次元
We're connected across 1, 2, and 3 dimensions!
ワンツースリーで飛び越えて
Let's leap over with a one, two, three!
今はもうネットもリアルです
Even the internet is real life now!
チックチック繋いで ラブアンドピース
Connecting tick-tick, love and peace!
ちくたくまわるまわる
Tick-tock, spinning 'round and 'round!
ときめきチャージ ときかけガール
Charging up excitement, a time-traveling girl!
スリーツースリーツースリーワン
Three, two, three, two, three, one!
待てれば大勝利 バーチャリアル
If you can wait, it's a huge win, Virtu-Real!
ちゅっちゅちゅ ちゅっちゅちゅ チェリーチェリーチュウチュウチュ
Chu, chu, chu! Chu, chu, chu! Cherry, cherry, chu, chu, chu!
しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment.
2025.10.1 Wed
Wednesday, October 1, 2025
8th Anniversary
with DJ ANKIMO
2019 1st year / 2020 2nd year
2021 3rd year
2022 4th year
2023 5th year
2024 6th year
ARE YOU READY?
8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party
降りわたる青い空に今日も
Today as well, in the clear blue sky,
弾け飛ぶ笑顔ひとつ咲かせたら
if I can make a bursting smile bloom,
本当は震えている
truth is, I'm actually trembling,
手足が隠せないよ
and I can't hide my shaking hands and feet.
踊る鼓動の先はいつも
Beyond my dancing heartbeat,
君ならではの色で描く
I always paint with colors unique to you.
崩れそうな足元も
Even on these unstable footsteps,
止められなかったこの想いも
and with these feelings that couldn't be stopped,
ツバメみたいに羽ばたく
I'll flap my wings like a swallow.
飛べたならいいのに
If only I could fly away...
もう何もいらないから
Since I don't need anything else anymore,
忘れさせないから
since I won't ever let you forget,
どこまでも遠く遠く
no matter how far, far away,
このまま連れ去って
just take me away like this.
手を繋いでいて
Hold my hand,
テイクアジャーニー
take a journey,
涙を拭くように
as if wiping away tears,
あの闇も越えて
let's cross over that darkness.
未知の翼広げて
Spreading our wings to the unknown,
誓うよ
I promise you,
駆け出す空へ
into the sky we run towards!
みんなー！
Everyone!
なくした鍵は見つかった
The lost key has been found.
乗り込むための切符なら掴んだ
I've grabbed the ticket to board.
いつの間にか進んでた
Before I knew it, I had moved forward,
君のスペシャルな夢の向こうへ
towards the other side of your special dream.
カモメみたいに青空へ
Like a seagull flying into the blue sky,
出かけたらいいのに
I wish I could head out.
気がつけば
But before I realized it,
檻の中にいて
I was inside a cage.
目と目で見つめ合って
Looking into each other's eyes,
僕らは
we...
きっと繋がっているから
are surely connected.
間違っても
Even if we make mistakes,
迷っても
even if we get lost,
立ち止まらないでいよう
let's keep moving without stopping.
空の果て
To the edge of the sky,
目指そうよ
let's aim.
この先を見つめて
Staring at what lies ahead,
飛び立つの
we will take flight,
この命かけて
risking this life of ours!
もう何もいらないから
Because I don't need anything else anymore,
忘れさせないから
because I won't let you forget...
どこまでも届くよ
It will reach anywhere
ありのままの君でいいよ
Just as you are is fine
きっと涙を
Surely the tears...
青い闇を越えて
...will cross the blue darkness.
いつだって笑っていてよ
Always keep smiling.
行こう 無限の向こうの空へ
Let's go to the sky beyond infinity.
いかないでー！
Don't go!
高鳴る心臓に彩りを乗せて
With colors riding on my beating heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
I paint an ambiguous dream.
幻想はさあ そのままで
Now, let the illusion remain as it is,
終わらせないで
and don't let it end.
答えをえんえんと探し続けて
Endlessly searching for an answer,
何もかも足りないと嘆いて
lamenting that everything is not enough.
さんざん降る夕立を ただ雨だとか
Dismissing the pouring evening shower as just rain,
優しく寄り添って
gently drawing close...
心が晴れるのならば
If my heart can clear up,
翼が生えたような
I feel as if wings...
気がして
...have sprouted.
いつだって隣にいたから
Because you were always by my side.
だって言葉紡いで歌うことが私の運命だ
Because weaving words and singing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた悲しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the common sadness in this world,
夜空に咲いた花のように暗闇を照らす
illuminating the darkness like a flower blooming in the night sky.
小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light.
名前も持たない僕らだけど
Though we don't even have names,
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge us.
ひとつひとつ枯れない花のように
Like withered flowers, one by one,
昨日の自分にさよならして 零れた涙
saying goodbye to yesterday's self, tears overflowed.
上手く笑えないの 見つけたんだ
I found that I can't smile well.
だって理想は遠く高くばかり遠ざかっちゃうよ
Because ideals only drift further, distant and high.
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって届かないの
No matter how much I stretch my hand and scream, it doesn't reach.
求めてばかりじゃ駄目だって信じているよ
I believe that just seeking isn't enough.
どうか歌よ響いて
Please, let my song resonate.
足元がからまる
My feet get tangled up.
行き止まりばっか足がすくんで立てないよ
Encountering only dead ends, my feet freeze and I can't stand.
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出すんだ
I'll find you and lead you out from this silent world.
言葉紡いで歌うことが私の運命だ
Weaving words and singing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた悲しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the common sadness in this world,
夜空に咲いた花のように暗闇を照らす
illuminating the darkness like a flower blooming in the night sky.
小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light.
君の隣で枯れたなら
If only I could wither by your side.
そうだ、ピース！
That's right, peace!
手をつなぐ
holding hands,
空、掲げて
holding high to the sky,
て・て・て・て
te-te-te-te...
タッチ！
Touch!
高鳴る 鳴らせて 胸躍るスパーキングだね
It's beating, make it ring, heart-dancing sparkling!
アバンチュール ラリラリラリー
Aventure, lari-lari-rally,
はち切れそうな未来
a future about to burst,
誰もが求めるウェーブだね
a wave that everyone is seeking!
8次元まで
To the 8th dimension!
連れ去って
...take me away!
地球ごとぐるぐる回る準備ができたっちゃって
I'm ready to spin around along with the whole Earth!
アバンチュラリラリラ
Aventurari-rari-ra
あっちゅー間に時代は巡り 宇宙の果て
In the blink of an eye, eras turn, to the end of space...
宇宙を走らせた
...running through space.
時代を先取りして
Anticipating the times,
さあ君の波へ
now, catch your wave!
無限大の可能性を
With infinite possibilities...
信じて
...believe!
超ウルトラハッピー！ めちゃくちゃグルーヴととのって
Super ultra happy! With our groove totally in place,
さあさあ踊り踊る超ウルトラハッピー！
come on, let's dance! Super ultra happy!
巡ってめぐってぐるぐる
Spinning and turning around and around,
この出会いにサンキュー
thank you for this encounter.
インフィニティの先へ
Beyond infinity!
ララララ...
La la la la...
てってってってそれ更新中
Updating right now!
ララララ...
La la la la...
表明する情感たたずんで
Standing with feelings revealed,
アバンチュラリラリラ
Aventurari-rari-ra
飛び込む光ファイルの山
diving into a mountain of light files.
アバンチュライトハッピー
Aventuright happy!
それそれそれそれそれと
This, that, and all of that...
僕らはさらに宇宙放って
We launch even further into space,
見せるわ
and I'll show you!
アバンチュラリラリラ
Aventurari-rari-ra
一人じゃいけないところまで
To a place we couldn't reach alone,
見せて
show me,
show me...
見せて！
Show me!
さあ 時代を超えて
Now, transcending eras,
さあ 君の声を",
now, let me hear your voice!
さあ 巡り続けるときを超え
Now, beyond the endlessly cycling time...
連れ去って
...take me away!
超デラックスなエネルギーが
A super deluxe energy
君とのメロディーに
melds into our melody.
一緒に見たい夢をここに
The dreams we want to share together,
いま
right here, now,
混ざり合い始めた
they've begun to intertwine...
永遠の輝き
...with an eternal brilliance.
超ウルトラハッピー！ めちゃくちゃグルーヴととのって
Super ultra happy! With our groove totally in place,
さあさあ踊り踊る超ウルトラハッピー！
come on, let's dance! Super ultra happy!
巡ってめぐってぐるぐる
Spinning and turning around and around,
この出会いにサンキュー
thank you for this encounter.
インフィニティの先へ
Beyond infinity!
ララララ...
La la la la...
てってってってそれ更新中
Updating right now!
ララララ...
La la la la...
超デラックスに
Super-deluxely,
いま更新中！
updating right now!
はい！みんな、こんそらー！
Yes! Hello, everyone! Kon-Sora!
みんなの声が大きすぎて
Everyone's voices are so loud
オケが聞こえないレベルの
that they're almost drowning out the backing track.
大歓声ありがとう！
Thank you so much for the massive cheers!
ちょっと、一回、息吸わせてもらっちゃおうかな
Let me catch my breath for just a second.
にゃは！
Nyaha!
ということで、1年半ぶりの
And so, this is my first solo live
ソロライブなんですけど
in a year and a half!
えっと、ちょっと恒例のやつやっていいですか？
Um, can I do that customary thing we always do?
みんなーー！
Everyone!
って言うんで、「はい」とか言ってください。いきますよ
I'll call out, so please respond with "Yes!" and so on. Here we go!
男の子ーー！
Boys!
ちょっと恥ずかしいかもしれない、手だけ振ってもいいよ
It might be a little embarrassing. You can just wave your hands!
女の子ーー！
Girls!
おお、声聞こえた！ありがとう！
Ooh, I heard you! Thank you!
海外の方ーー！
People from overseas!
おお、すごい！
Ooh, amazing!
そして、そうだなぁ
And, let me see...
めっちゃ遠くから来たよって人。絶対自分が一番遠いみたいな人、いる？
Anyone who came from super far away? Like, "I definitely traveled the furthest"?
あ、でも海外の方かな？ありがとうございます！
Ah, probably someone from overseas? Thank you so much!
そして、
And next...
そうだな、未成年の方ーー！
Let's see, minors!
いや、ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you very much!
では、みんなでいくよ
Now, let's do one all together.
みんなーー！
Everyone!
こっち側ーー！
This side!
That side!
最後に
And finally...
全員ーー！
Everyone!
ありがとーー！
Thank you!
はい！というわけで、これがね、やりたかったんです。ずっと
Yes! That was exactly what I've been wanting to do for ages.
えー、おっちー！あははっ。
Eh? Hello! Ahaha.
というわけでですね、なんと
So, actually, everyone...
YouTubeで見ている皆さん、無料配信は
those watching on YouTube, the free broadcast...
ここまでなんです！
ends here!
「えー、今来たばっかり」？私も今来たばっかり！
"Huh? But I just got here!" I just got here, too!
そうだよね、分かる分かる。
I know, I totally understand.
えー、分かってるよ。コメントのみんなも見えてるよ。
Yes, I know. I can see everyone in the comments, too.
「イェーイ」って言ってるなー。イェー、ちょっとラグってるのかもしれない。
You're saying "Yay!" Yay... though there might be some lag.
「今来たばっかり」って書いてね、よろしく！あははっ。
Please write "I just got here," okay? Thank you! Ahaha.
はぁ...
Whew...
続きは、えー、見たい人、概要欄から
If you want to watch the rest, please check the description box...
見てもらえると... どこにあるのかな？
and click... Wait, where is it?
ふふっ、どっかに概要欄が多分あるんで、
Hehe, there should be a description box somewhere,
ここら辺からちょっと見てもらえれば、
so if you could check it out there,
嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy!
よぉし。はぁ...
Alright. Whew...
ちょっと...
Give me a second...
次の曲行っちゃおうかな？
Shall we move on to the next song?
まだまだ盛り上がれる？
Are you ready to get even more hyped?
みんながおうちに帰ってくるの、待ってたよ。
I've been waiting for everyone to come back home.
というわけで、次の曲は新アルバムからこの曲です！
So, the next song is this one from my new album!
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。★ライブチケット購入はコチラ
[The free broadcast ends here. ★Click here to purchase tickets]
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ
The free preview broadcast ends here.
★Click here to purchase live tickets